printivo.com 2014-11-03

# printivo.com | Privacy Policy

At Printivo, we believe that you should be fully aware of how their information taking from you is used - so we’ve put together this document to explain exactly what data we take and how we approach handling your data.

Before you read it, the most important thing you need to know is this: your privacy is as important to us as it is to you. It is an act of love and trust for you to have given us your data, we value and one that we take seriously. We will never show your details to anyone else, sell, rent or otherwise disclose any of your personal information, including your email address, to any third party without your prior and explicit consent. And unless you give us specific consent to act otherwise, the following Privacy policy legal document outlines how Printivo.com handles your private information.

We’ve tried to make it as transparent and easy to understand as possible

**1\. Collection and use of personal information**

Printivo Ltd. collects your personal information when you use our website:

**What we collect**

·         Full name

·         Username

·         Password

·         Email address

·         Business Type

·         Postal Address

·         Telephone number

  **2\. How we use it**

·         To communicate with you on Printivo-related matters

·         To provide you with order and billing history information

·         Updating Your Personal Information

·         To help us reach you for delivery of your print products

·         To notify you of special offerings and bonuses on Printivo.com

 Printivo does not store your card and payment details, all credit card transactions are routed through our third party payment gateway, _Interswitch._

If you want to change your name, e-mail address, password, and/or preferred communication method after you’ve registered, you can access your account in the Your Account section of Printivo.com. 

If you prefer to do this by speaking directly to someone at Printivo, you can contact us directly, and we’ll be happy to help.

**3\. Introducing Cookies – what are they?**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user.  Printivo.com make use of cookies. Which are placed both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer`s hard drive. Printivo.com`s cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

Cookies are really nothing to get worried about. They’re simply tiny text files stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages.

Printivo Ltd use Cookies to improve the quality of our service and make it easier for you to use. We do this by storing your preferences in Cookies and by tracking user trends - for example, we use Cookies to allow you to automatically log into Printivo.com after your first session – basically, eliminating the need to remember and type in your username and password.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. 

We also have relationships with carefully selected suppliers (nice ones!) who may also set Cookies during your visit to be used for remarketing purposes - in other words, to show you different products and services that you might be interested in. If you`d like to opt out, you may like to use the tools provided by the Network Advertising Initiative website.

**4\. Information Sharing And Disclosure**

Printivo protects your personal information. However, we may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

Printivo.com and its affiliates may share some of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to third parties make a legally compliant request for its disclosure.

**5.Links to Other Sites**

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you.Printivo.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, content or other activities of such linked websites.

**6\. Advertisements on Printivo.com**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**7\. Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Occasionally,  Printivo.com will review and possibly change or edit this policy in accordance with potential changes to our business and as required by law. You will be notified of such changes. Printivo Ltd. reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time.

**8\. Got more Questions?**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: info@printivocom

© Printivo Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
